{"qid": "easy-flight-0000", "question": "What was the departure time of the AA2319 flight from MIA to LAS on 2022-06-05?", "answer": "21:43"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0001", "question": "What was the departure time of the AA4869 flight from HHH to CLT on 2022-05-06?", "answer": "12:16"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0002", "question": "What was the departure time of the DL5172 flight from SBN to ATL on 2022-01-03?", "answer": "12:33"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0003", "question": "What was the departure time of the DL891 flight from SEA to LAX on 2022-01-22?", "answer": "11:54"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0004", "question": "What was the departure time of the DL414 flight from LGA to ATL on 2022-02-07?", "answer": "18:45"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0005", "question": "What was the departure time of the DL2759 flight from MCO to DTW on 2022-05-14?", "answer": "16:49"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0006", "question": "What was the departure time of the DL82 flight from MEM to ATL on 2022-01-18?", "answer": "12:53"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0007", "question": "What was the departure time of the WN2392 flight from PDX to OAK on 2022-04-12?", "answer": "13:18"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0008", "question": "What was the departure time of the F9124 flight from JAX to SJU on 2022-02-28?", "answer": "11:25"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0009", "question": "What was the departure time of the AA2792 flight from SAT to DFW on 2022-01-07?", "answer": "7:51"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0010", "question": "Was the flight DL5097 from MLU to ATL cancelled on 2022-02-05?", "answer": "No"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0011", "question": "Was the flight AS715 from EWR to SEA cancelled on 2022-03-11?", "answer": "No"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0012", "question": "Was the flight UA2106 from LAS to IAH cancelled on 2022-02-05?", "answer": "No"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0013", "question": "Was the flight AA6152 from CHO to CLT cancelled on 2022-07-06?", "answer": "No"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0014", "question": "Was the flight UA3981 from TVC to ORD cancelled on 2022-03-18?", "answer": "No"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0015", "question": "Was the flight UA348 from OGG to ORD cancelled on 2022-06-29?", "answer": "No"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0016", "question": "Was the flight WN5333 from RDU to BWI cancelled on 2022-01-08?", "answer": "No"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0017", "question": "Was the flight WN2465 from SAN to DEN cancelled on 2022-01-10?", "answer": "No"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0018", "question": "Was the flight AA5566 from CLT to LEX cancelled on 2022-01-20?", "answer": "No"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0019", "question": "Was the flight AA2289 from MIA to LAX cancelled on 2022-02-20?", "answer": "No"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0020", "question": "What is the flight number of the SkyWest Airlines Inc. flight from IAH to PIB on 2022-06-24?", "answer": "5107"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0021", "question": "What is the flight number of the Delta Air Lines Inc. flight from MCO to LGA on 2022-04-30?", "answer": "2873, 1176, 1340, 2398"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0022", "question": "What is the flight number of the Mesa Airlines Inc. flight from IAH to RDU on 2022-01-12?", "answer": "6081"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0023", "question": "What is the flight number of the Alaska Airlines Inc. flight from RDU to SEA on 2022-06-18?", "answer": "905, 1309"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0024", "question": "What is the flight number of the Commutair Aka Champlain Enterprises, Inc. flight from CHO to IAD on 2022-01-07?", "answer": "4258"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0025", "question": "What is the flight number of the Southwest Airlines Co. flight from MIA to BWI on 2022-02-11?", "answer": "159, 836, 1185, 1647"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0026", "question": "What is the flight number of the Frontier Airlines Inc. flight from SJU to MCO on 2022-07-14?", "answer": "111, 105, 107"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0027", "question": "What is the flight number of the Delta Air Lines Inc. flight from BOS to MCO on 2022-06-06?", "answer": "1400, 1555, 2974"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0028", "question": "What is the flight number of the Delta Air Lines Inc. flight from ATL to MIA on 2022-01-27?", "answer": "1372, 1381, 1538, 2251, 2279, 2301, 2352, 2860"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0029", "question": "What is the flight number of the Southwest Airlines Co. flight from ONT to LAS on 2022-07-08?", "answer": "1452, 1683, 2007, 2078, 2663"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0030", "question": "How long was the different between the CRS recorded departure time and actual departure time of the DL5273 flight from JFK to CVG on 2022-03-29?", "answer": "5"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0031", "question": "How long was the different between the CRS recorded departure time and actual departure time of the WN573 flight from PHX to SMF on 2022-04-15?", "answer": "30"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0032", "question": "How long was the different between the CRS recorded departure time and actual departure time of the DL3826 flight from LAX to ABQ on 2022-06-15?", "answer": "6"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0033", "question": "How long was the different between the CRS recorded departure time and actual departure time of the B6792 flight from TPA to BOS on 2022-01-13?", "answer": "44"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0034", "question": "How long was the different between the CRS recorded departure time and actual departure time of the DL5233 flight from MSP to CVG on 2022-07-21?", "answer": "53"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0035", "question": "How long was the different between the CRS recorded departure time and actual departure time of the DL712 flight from ATL to IND on 2022-06-08?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0036", "question": "How long was the different between the CRS recorded departure time and actual departure time of the AA2020 flight from TPA to CLT on 2022-02-07?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0037", "question": "How long was the different between the CRS recorded departure time and actual departure time of the UA3430 flight from EWR to RDU on 2022-06-10?", "answer": "11"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0038", "question": "How long was the different between the CRS recorded departure time and actual departure time of the AA1235 flight from DFW to LAX on 2022-07-31?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0039", "question": "How long was the different between the CRS recorded departure time and actual departure time of the UA3831 flight from SBN to ORD on 2022-06-13?", "answer": "16"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0040", "question": "How long did UA3449 delay when arrival on 2022-03-24?", "answer": "15.0"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0041", "question": "How long did UA5482 delay when arrival on 2022-06-06?", "answer": "124.0"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0042", "question": "How long did AS218 delay when arrival on 2022-03-24?", "answer": "26.0"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0043", "question": "How long did AA4631 delay when arrival on 2022-06-27?", "answer": "19.0"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0044", "question": "How long did WN4822 delay when arrival on 2022-07-30?", "answer": "2.0"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0045", "question": "How long did G42595 delay when arrival on 2022-04-03?", "answer": "62.0"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0046", "question": "How long did WN2519 delay when arrival on 2022-02-21?", "answer": "3.0"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0047", "question": "How long did DL3541 delay when arrival on 2022-04-24?", "answer": "399.0"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0048", "question": "How long did NK3055 delay when arrival on 2022-02-17?", "answer": "nan"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0049", "question": "How long did AS3388 delay when arrival on 2022-02-12?", "answer": "28.0"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0050", "question": "How many extra minutes did the WN2522 flight take from ECP to ATL on 2022-03-27?", "answer": "-10.0"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0051", "question": "How many extra minutes did the DL2058 flight take from MCO to RDU on 2022-04-13?", "answer": "-10.0"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0052", "question": "How many extra minutes did the WN1749 flight take from MKE to DCA on 2022-05-23?", "answer": "-1.0"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0053", "question": "How many extra minutes did the B6257 flight take from BOS to BZN on 2022-03-26?", "answer": "-13.0"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0054", "question": "How many extra minutes did the WN2361 flight take from AUS to FLL on 2022-06-16?", "answer": "-19.0"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0055", "question": "How many extra minutes did the HA73 flight take from ONT to HNL on 2022-01-13?", "answer": "-28.0"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0056", "question": "How many extra minutes did the WN1415 flight take from ATL to LGA on 2022-01-02?", "answer": "-14.0"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0057", "question": "How many extra minutes did the AA1855 flight take from AUS to SJU on 2022-07-13?", "answer": "13.0"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0058", "question": "How many extra minutes did the AA5027 flight take from DCA to PWM on 2022-04-12?", "answer": "-9.0"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0059", "question": "How many extra minutes did the DL5698 flight take from DCA to JFK on 2022-07-01?", "answer": "23.0"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0060", "question": "What was the local arrival time of the NK143 flight from BQN to MCO on 2022-02-16?", "answer": "5:52"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0061", "question": "What was the local arrival time of the WN6075 flight from DEN to ATL on 2022-01-07?", "answer": "17:31"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0062", "question": "What was the local arrival time of the UA504 flight from IAD to LAX on 2022-01-28?", "answer": "8:57"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0063", "question": "What was the local arrival time of the NK1314 flight from FLL to DEN on 2022-06-11?", "answer": "22:53"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0064", "question": "What was the local arrival time of the B61168 flight from PBI to HPN on 2022-01-05?", "answer": "23:44"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0065", "question": "What was the local arrival time of the UA5415 flight from IAH to COS on 2022-07-21?", "answer": "11:10"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0066", "question": "What was the local arrival time of the WN1360 flight from BWI to LAS on 2022-01-23?", "answer": "8:10"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0067", "question": "What was the local arrival time of the DL4872 flight from TYS to LGA on 2022-03-28?", "answer": "16:43"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0068", "question": "What was the local arrival time of the AA2281 flight from DFW to SAT on 2022-03-08?", "answer": "19:03"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0069", "question": "What was the local arrival time of the DL5165 flight from XNA to MSP on 2022-01-17?", "answer": "19:00"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0070", "question": "What was the CRS-recorded arrival time of the AA2733 flight from DFW to LAX on 2022-01-30?", "answer": "23:59"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0071", "question": "What was the CRS-recorded arrival time of the B61075 flight from PVD to MCO on 2022-02-11?", "answer": "19:23"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0072", "question": "What was the CRS-recorded arrival time of the NK1697 flight from OAK to LAS on 2022-05-24?", "answer": "22:29"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0073", "question": "What was the CRS-recorded arrival time of the WN1111 flight from SJC to LAS on 2022-05-02?", "answer": "16:40"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0074", "question": "What was the CRS-recorded arrival time of the G42148 flight from SAV to CVG on 2022-07-08?", "answer": "8:05"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0075", "question": "What was the CRS-recorded arrival time of the UA2240 flight from ORD to CHS on 2022-07-29?", "answer": "22:07"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0076", "question": "What was the CRS-recorded arrival time of the AA6104 flight from SYR to BOS on 2022-06-20?", "answer": "20:10"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0077", "question": "What was the CRS-recorded arrival time of the B61586 flight from MCO to BUF on 2022-05-23?", "answer": "17:06"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0078", "question": "What was the CRS-recorded arrival time of the AA1683 flight from CLT to DTW on 2022-03-17?", "answer": "9:02"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0079", "question": "What was the CRS-recorded arrival time of the UA4425 flight from EWR to DCA on 2022-06-29?", "answer": "8:17"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0080", "question": "How long was the flight NK115 from MCO to BDL on 2022-07-08?", "answer": "142"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0081", "question": "How long was the flight AS809 from PDX to OGG on 2022-02-11?", "answer": "332"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0082", "question": "How long was the flight UA5045 from DVL to JMS on 2022-03-10?", "answer": "31"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0083", "question": "How long was the flight DL441 from DTW to ATL on 2022-05-09?", "answer": "81"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0084", "question": "How long was the flight UA662 from EWR to DFW on 2022-04-22?", "answer": "179"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0085", "question": "How long was the flight AA793 from BHM to DFW on 2022-05-01?", "answer": "96"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0086", "question": "How long was the flight WN327 from TPA to BNA on 2022-03-01?", "answer": "92"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0087", "question": "How long was the flight AA3016 from PSP to PHX on 2022-01-23?", "answer": "48"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0088", "question": "How long was the flight UA5286 from DEN to ICT on 2022-03-11?", "answer": "58"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0089", "question": "How long was the flight AA6030 from PHL to BGR on 2022-05-08?", "answer": "77"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0090", "question": "How many minutes did the DL3538 flight take to taxi in on 2022-06-26?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0091", "question": "How many minutes did the AS617 flight take to taxi in on 2022-02-26?", "answer": "11"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0092", "question": "How many minutes did the WN1069 flight take to taxi in on 2022-02-02?", "answer": "6"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0093", "question": "How many minutes did the UA450 flight take to taxi in on 2022-07-31?", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0094", "question": "How many minutes did the AA802 flight take to taxi in on 2022-03-25?", "answer": "12"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0095", "question": "How many minutes did the WN1537 flight take to taxi in on 2022-03-13?", "answer": "5"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0096", "question": "How many minutes did the AA4804 flight take to taxi in on 2022-02-20?", "answer": "8"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0097", "question": "How many minutes did the B6623 flight take to taxi in on 2022-05-05?", "answer": "32"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0098", "question": "How many minutes did the DL4967 flight take to taxi in on 2022-04-13?", "answer": "9"}
{"qid": "easy-flight-0099", "question": "How many minutes did the WN2517 flight take to taxi in on 2022-02-08?", "answer": "6"}
